yalieastafrica.org 2017-04-10

# YALI - Privacy

## Privacy Notice

Thank you for visiting this website for the YALI Regional Leadership Center, East Africa – Nairobi. Your privacy and security are very important to us. Please be aware that Deloitte or USAID do not collect or track any personal information when you visit this website, unless you choose to provide that information. However, we do collect some technical information about your visit. We use this information, in the aggregate, to make our website more useful to visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology used, to detect operational problems, and to improve the website's overall security. The information we may receive from you varies based on what you do when visiting our site. We do automatically collect and store the name of the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website (such as a search engine or referring page) from which you reached our site. We use the information we collect to count the number of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

You are not required to provide any personal information to view this website. You may, however, choose to provide your contact and other personal information to the YALI Regional Leadership Center, East Africa – Nairobi in order to apply to participate in the training courses offered by the Center.

We will only use your personal information for the purpose for which it was provided, namely to evaluate your application to participate in the programs of the YALI Regional Leadership Center, East Africa – Nairobi. When you voluntarily click the “Submit” button on any of the Web forms found on this site, you are indicating your voluntary consent to the use of the information you submit, for the stated purpose.

In addition, we use Google Analytics to provide us with demographic information that is not personally identifiable. This information may include, among other things, gender, age, and interests. We use this information in a variety of ways. For example, we may use this information to help analyze our site traffic, understand our visitors and what they care about, and to improve our services. We use these data only in the aggregate form as provided directly from Google Analytics. We will retain this information for as long as we have this site. We will not disclose this information to any other third party.

IF YOU SEND US E-MAIL

You may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. 

THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND APPLICATIONS

We link to social networking and other kinds of third-party websites. We use social networking websites to interact with audiences and to engage in marketing and public dialogue. We also use web measurement and customization technologies to measure the number of visitors to our websites and their various sections and to help make our websites more useful to visitors. In some cases, the third-party application may request an e-mail address, username, password, and geographic location for account registration purposes. We do not use third-party websites to solicit and collect personally identifiable information from individuals. We do not collect or store any personally identifiable information collected by any third-party website, and no personally identifiable information will be disclosed, sold or transferred to any other entity outside of the YALI Program, unless required for law enforcement purposes or by statute.

INFORMATION COLLECTED FOR TRACKING AND CUSTOMIZATION (COOKIES)

A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to your computer to allow it to remember specific information about your session while you are connected. Your computer will only share the information in the cookie with the website that provided it, and no other website can request it. There are two types of cookies: 

Session: Session cookies last only as long as your web browser is open. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted. Websites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site.

Persistent: Persistent cookies are saved on a user’s hard drive in order to determine which users are new to the site or are repeat visitors.

If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn cookies off in your browser. You will still have access to all information and resources on our website. However, turning off cookies may affect the functioning of some websites. Be aware that disabling cookies in your browser will affect cookie usage at all other websites you visit as well.

LINKS TO EXTERNAL WEBSITES

Our website has many links to other organizations, U.S. agencies, embassies, multilateral organizations, and private organizations in both the United States and other nations. When you follow a link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

ACURRACY OF INFORMATION

Every effort is made to provide accurate and complete information. However, we cannot guarantee that there will be no errors. With respect to documents and information on this website, neither USAID, Deloitte East Africa or the YALI Regional Leadership Center, East Africa – Nairobi, nor its employees, contractors or partners make any warranty, expressed or implied, including the warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose with respect to documents available from this website. Additionally, the YALI Regional Leadership Center, East Africa – Nairobi assumes no legal liability for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, product, or process disclosed herein and does not represent that use of such information, product, or process would not infringe on privately owned rights.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we reserve the right to use software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986. Information also may be used for authorized law enforcement investigations. Except for the above purposes, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on these web sites are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution.
